# **ALI PAJAND**

ali.pajand@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/alipajand/ 🔘 github.com/alipajand



# Senior Frontend Developer

# Summary

I'm an extroverted, energetic, highly positive and hardworking developer with expertise in web development specific to the frontend side with a history of graphics knowledge.

My main aim is to learn about the web and new technologies from various sources. I believe users should experience a rich and thought-through form of art whereas developers should be making use of reusable and simple codes.

# Work Experience

Mar 2018 - Present

### Senior Frontend Developer

#### Ctrl+Tech

- Implement websites and admin panels for "Tazebar", "Bidzila", "Techtoman", "Admartiz", "3sootjobs", "FirouzehPlat" and "Sahamdaran" and also two alpha version of projects that are coming soon. All these projects based on <u>Vue.js</u> and <u>nuxt.js</u>
- Worked with bootstrap-vue and vuetify
- Web application (PWAs) for all products like "Tazebar", "Techtoman"
- Attractive online chat room in 3sootjobs with Firebase messaging service
- Work with <u>Socket.io</u> in bidzila to handle all bids for all auctions
- Rewrite old applications, maintain and fix bugs
- Implement custom service worker with workbox to manage all notifications

Jan 2014 - Dec 2017

#### Frontend Developer

### Rayvarz Software Engineering

Working almost standard, open source, functional, participating in design and developing new products and discussing about requirements with business analysts

- Design pattern mentoring, UI Discussion and prepare prototype for programmers
- Working in BPMS team as frontend developer (business process management system to rewrite online admin panel and portal in Vue.js)
- Working in Portal team and collaborate on service catalogue for MEFA (Ministry of Economic Affairs and Finance, Deputy of Economic Affairs of Iran) in Vue.js
- Change user interface of eOffice to create new sense and change admin panel arguments and texts
- Maintenance of old eOffice application and add feature
- Start to implement new website version of rayvarz
- Try to integrate UI of all products in whole company

Jun 2013 - Sep 2013

### Internship Frontend Developer

Unilever (Iran Department)

Help to develop and maintain the global application

	Remo	ote Experiences
Apr 2019 - Jul 2019	Frontend Developer (Vancouver Area, Canada)  Timely	
	Help to develop and mainta	ain the global application
Jan 2015 - Jan 2017	Front-end Developer (Lahti Area, Finland)	
	Lahtiprecision  Maintenance and implementing three generation of website (Persian Language)	
		Education —
Sep 2014 - Aug 2018	M.Sc. Computer/Information Technology Administration  Allame Tabataba'i University	
	Thesis: Identification of Factors to Use Cloud Computing by University Students in Educationa Process	
Sep 2010 - Aug 2014	B.Sc. Engineering/Industrial Management  Allame Tabataba'i University	
		Skills —
Vue js   Nuxt js		React js   Next js   Gatsby
<ul> <li>- Nuxt is my favorite ssr framework in vue</li> <li>- State management tools like Vuex</li> <li>- Familiar with typescript</li> </ul>		<ul> <li>- Next is my favorite ssr framework in vue</li> <li>- State management tools like Redux</li> <li>- Familiar with typescript</li> </ul>
React Native		Unit Tests
Familiar with typescript		BDD and TDD tests with <b>Jest</b> , <b>Mocha</b> and <b>E2E</b>
Notifications and Service Workers		Progressive Web Apps (PWA)
Services like <b>Onesignal</b> and <b>Google Firebase</b>		Experience enough by working with <b>PWA</b> and <b>Workbox</b>
Version Controller		Python (Django) & Nodejs
Working with <b>Git</b> , <b>SVN</b> and <b>TFS</b>		- Familiar as a backend background and web api

## Latest Noticeable Projects

### All Following Projects are Beyond Work Experiences that were Mentioned Above in CTRLTECH company:

(Like: "Tazebar", "Bidzila", "Techtoman", "Admartiz", "Banikar", "FirouzehPlat" and "Sahamdaran")

#### • Didbaan

An Online shop for spadsystem company

Beta Version: 2021

#### Neuralet

Neuralet adaptation is an open-source platform for edge deep learning models on GPU, TPU, and more.

Website: 2021

### • Zellai

Zellai is a platform for Finding the best resources based on your path to learning business skills and help people to find their road map easily!

Beta Version | Admin: 2021

#### • Hedio

Hedio is a platform for requesting to your favorite talents to record a video for you or your business. It has two types of view in desktop and mobile application (PWA).

PWA Version: 2021

### • 3Click (Hotel, Flight, Tour and Train Ticket Reservation System)

3Click is a platform for Deltaban Company in Iran which has two side of selling tickets and organizing abroad tours. Both these platform have the same features but 3click is economic one. It has two types of view in desktop and mobile application (PWA).

Go to Link: 2020

### • Tazehbar Microservice (Tazero, Tazechin, Tazejoo)

Tazebar is a B2B tech farm-to-table platform in Iran, aiming to supply fresh ingredients for Horeca. This project has some subsystems for different works. It has a lot of panels for its services to manage all the processes and PWA application for web views. It has two different views in desktop and mobile application (PWA).

Tazebar | Tazero | Tazechin: 2019 - 2020

### • Ragabit

Online Cryptocurrency Exchange website

Go to Link: 2021

### OZZO

Online podcast application for sharing books, podcast and video based on laravel blazor

Go to Link: 2020

### • Golgift

Online shopping store for flowers in Iran and some other countries for delivery flowers and send them postal cards too.

Go to Link: 2018 to present (for maintenance)

Created with **TVisualCV**